applypanonline.com 2014-03-30

# eMudhra - Privacy Policy for PAN Card Apply Online

We are sensitive to privacy issues and have established this Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. This privacy policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms and conditions. We, at eMudhra.com, respect your privacy and the confidentiality of your Personal Information (including email address, phone numbers and mail address etc. Only authorized personnel/employees of eMudhra have access to Your Personal Information specifically permitted by You for our use by us or for any other purpose. Our company's resources and entire staff are fully committed to safeguarding your personal data i.e. email address phone numbers, and mail address etc. we provide highest security and other precautionary measures are in place to protect your non-public information. We only collect, store and use your personal information (including email address , phone numbers and mail address etc) for defined purposes.We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the Website to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by our Website. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

####  Changes to Our Privacy Statement

From time to time we may revise this privacy notice. It is your obligation that you visit the website regularly and make yourself aware of any changes we make to this Privacy Statement, including a material change in the way we use your personal information and it will be deemed to be notified to and read by you on your using the Website once we post the same on our Website since the same is available.

####  Security Measures

At eMudhra.com, we use the industry-standard Secured Socket Layer (SSL) protocol which provides data encryption, message integrity, and server authentication when your data is sent to us. When you see a small lock at the bottom right or left corner of your browser window, you know your data is being encrypted for transmission. All information (including email address) you enter while using eMudhra.com is used to provide the services requested by you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information (including email address and phone numbers). All data is stored on eMudhra.com servers and is backed up to prevent the loss of data. Access to (and the use thereof) personally identifiable customer information (including email address and phone numbers) is restricted to authorized personnel as dictated by service, support, and / or fulfillment requirements.

####  Service Alerts and Critical Notices

Although we respect and honor your privacy preferences, eMudhra.com shall maintain the right to contact You when it is required to make You aware of changes (that are of a non-marketing nature), that may impact Your ability to use eMudhra.com products and services or to provide you with another alert irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under the Do not Disturb (DND) or Do Not Call (DNC) service.

####  Support Section

[www.eMudhra.com/pancard](http://www.emudhra.com/pancard) offers technical support and customer service to our customers. You may choose to submit a question through (email, phone call or mail) the support section of the Website or contact our support staff directly.It is used to research your problem, provide answers, and / or request more information. If you make a suggestion using the Feedback section of our Website, the suggestion alone may be stored, but no personal data (including email address, phone number and mail address etc) will be stored with the suggestion. eMudhra.com does retain the right to use your suggestions and product enhancement ideas to improve the Websites and product line without obligation to you. 

####  Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose Your information (including your email address email address, phone number and mail address etc) as and when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process or other judicial, administrative or investigative proceedings served or initiated on our Website. IN THE EVENT OF LEAKAGE OF ANY SUCH INFORMATION FROM THE WEBSITE FOR ANY REASON BEYOND THE CONTROL OF EMUDHRA.COM, EMUDHRA.COM SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE UNDER SUCH CIRCUMSTANCES AND NO ACTION SHALL LIE AGAINST EMUDHRA.COM.

####  Limitation of Warranties

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary mentioned herein, the maximum liability that eMudhra.com and / or its directors, employees, agents, representatives and authors shall be liable would not exceed the amount paid by you to eMudhra.com . Nothing contained herein shall mean that eMudhra.com and / or its directors, employees, agents, representatives and authors shall accept any liability that you or your representatives may notify but in case it is so done, it will be subject to our independent review of the same and our rights of defence. eMudhra.com in providing its services makes no warranties of any kind whatsoever. eMudhra.com shall have no liability for any errors, malfunctions and /or Loss of data or defects resulting from or related to the use of the information (including software) in the systems used for providing services herein. eMudhra.com shall not be liable to you for any indirect, Special or consequential damages or loss of profits arising from or related to the services provided or the information (including software) used for providing services.

####  Governing Law and Jurisdiction

The relationship between you and eMudhra.com shall be governed by the Laws of India. You and eMudhra.com agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located at Bangalore, India.
